let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the maximum permissible length of a bat in cricket?",
    answer: "38 inches",
    options: [
      "41 inches",
      "38 inches",
      "36 inches",
      "32 inches"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many squares or squares are there in the game of chess?",
    answer: "64",
    options: [
      "64",
      "65",
      "66",
      "67"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who won the first Olympic medal individually for independent India?",
    answer: "K D Jadhav",
    options: [
      "Milkha Singh",
      "Dhyan Chand",
      "K D Jadhav",
      "Vishwanathan Anand"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The quickest possible checkmate is in?",
    answer: "2 moves",
    options: [
      "3 moves",
      "5 moves",
      "4 moves",
      "2 moves"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "who is the most goal scorer in football international after Ronaldo and Messi?",
    answer: "Sunil Chetri",
    options: [
      "Kylian Mbappe",
      "Neymar Jr",
      "Sunil Chetri",
      "Erling Haaland"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the length of the cricket pitch?",
    answer: "20.12 meters",
    options: [
      "20.12 meters",
      "20.19 meters",
      "20.30 meters",
      "20.50 meters"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who became the first cricketer to hit 6 sixes in one day international criket?",
    answer: "Herschelle Gibs",
    options: [
      "Yuvraj Singh",
      "Herschelle Gibs",
      "Vivian Richards",
      "Kieron Pollards"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many Kabaddi World Cup titles are held by Indian Men's Kabaddi team?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which chess player recently overcame Vishy Anand and became India No.1?",
    answer: "Dommaraju Gukesh",
    options: [
      "Vidit Santosh Gujrathi",
      "Arjun Erigaisi",
      "Dommaraju Gukesh",
      "Harikrishna Pentala"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who won 2022 FIDE Candidates Chess tournament?",
    answer: "Ian Nepomniachtchi",
    options: [
      "Ian Nepomniachtchi",
      "Alireza Firouzja",
      "Jan-Krzysztof Duda",
      "Ding Liren"
    ]
  },
];

